piratebay.com 2014-10-12

# PRIVACY POLICY - PirateBay.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Bladebook, LLC (“we,” “us,” or “our”) wants to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect information from all end users of our Internet services (the “Services”), including those who access our Services (“Visitors”), what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**How Your Personal Information Is Collected and Used**

**Introduction**

** ** We collect information in different ways from our Visitors who access the various parts of our Services on our website located at www.Piratebay.com (the “Site”). We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services, and generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.

**Our Company Partners and Sponsors**

Some products and services may be offered to Visitors in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, you will be notified before any such data is collected or transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or feature.

Additionally, our partners may have advertisements or co-branded Web Pages that are cosponsored by an affiliate, independent contractor seller, or non-affiliated partner. We may share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered.

**Online Advertisements**

We may display our online advertisements. In those cases we share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors collected through, among other things, online surveys and promotions with these advertisers.

Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture company tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display or send the advertisement to the intended audience. We do not share personal information about our Visitors with these advertisers or joint venture companies.

**Responses to Email Inquiries**

When Visitors send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. We do not use the return email address for any other purpose and do not share the return email address with any third party.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys**

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our Visitors to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to our customer surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other Visitors we may have, to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

**Special Cases**

It is our policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

However, we may disclose personal information about Visitors, or information regarding your use of the Services or websites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Use, or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect us and our Visitors.

**“Cookies” and How We Use Them**

A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. We may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.

If you are a Visitor we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore, we restrict the Site to persons eighteen years or older.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THE SITE (UNLESS YOU GET YOUR PARENT’S OR GUARDIAN’S PERMISSION). IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THE SITE FOR ANY REASON (UNLESS YOU GET YOUR PARENT’S OR GUARDIAN’S PERMISSION). DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THE SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THE SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.

The Site is not aimed at children under 13 years old and we will not collect, use, provide or process in any other form any personal information of children under the age of 13 deliberately. We therefore also ask you, if you are under 13 years old, please do not send us your personal information (for example, your name, address and email address).

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or affiliates for those third parties or affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit an email request to Support@Piratebay.com. In your request, please specify that you want a “Your California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least 30 days for a response.

**Our California Do Not Track Policy**

We do not track our Visitors over time and/or across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, you can modify the preferences on your browser to set the DNT signal so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked. Please consult your browser for instructions on how to change the preferences to “Do Not Track.”

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

The Service and Site we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

**Visitors of Our Site from Outside the United States**

The Site’s offices are located in the United States. If you visit the Site from another country, please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the Site may be processed in and transferred to the United States and will be subject to U.S. law. U.S. privacy and data protection laws may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence. By using the Site or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in the United States.

**Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us by sending an e-mail to Support@Piratebay.com.

**Revisions to This Policy**

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Use of this agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.

Last Updated: June 4, 2014
